[
  {
    "name": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "food",
    "theme": "green",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Name the Italian, semi-soft, rich cheese with blue veins through it.",
        "options": [
          "Ricotta",
          "Blue Cheese",
          "Gorgonzola",
          "Parmesan"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "Coffee beans contain more caffeine than tea leaves.",
        "answer": false
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "What are the three ingredients in mead (spices excluded)?",
        "options": [
          "Sugar",
          "Honey",
          "Cinnamon",
          "Water",
          "Brown Sugar",
          "Yeast",
          "Salt"
        ],
        "answer": [
          1,
          3,
          5
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What crop does the Colorado Beetle attack?",
        "options": [
          "Corn",
          "Garlic",
          "Potato",
          "Wheat"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select-item",
        "question": "What vegetable did Mark Twain describe as “cabbage with a college education”?",
        "options": [
          "Spinach",
          "Broccoli",
          "Cauliflower",
          "Kale"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "What name is given to a sugar syrup which is gently heated until it browns?",
        "answer": "Caramel"
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "In Which city was chop suey invented?",
        "options": [
          "Hong Kong",
          "Taipei",
          "New York",
          "San Francisco"
        ],
        "answer": [3]
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "One of the fattiest fishes is salmon. 4 ounces contains how many grams of fat?",
        "min": 1,
        "max": 10,
        "answer": 9
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "In which American State did chili con carne originate?",
        "answer": "Texas"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What is the correct name for a cluster or bunch of bananas?",
        "options": [
          "Foot",
          "Hand",
          "Flock",
          "Pod"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "knowledge",
    "theme": "yellow",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "fill-blank",
        "question": "Mole is a popular paste in Mexico. Mole is a mixture of chili’s and what other tasty ingredient?",
        "answer": "Chocolate"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "What is the name of the famous art deco skyscraper in New York City?",
        "options": [
          "Trump Tower",
          "Chrysler building",
          "Empire State Building",
          "The New York Times Building"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "multi-select",
        "question": "Select the names of “The Three Musketeers”.",
        "options": [
          "Chevy",
          "Topeka",
          "Athos",
          "Duke",
          "Porthos",
          "John Felton",
          "Aramis"
        ],
        "answer": [
          2,
          4,
          6
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": "toggle-translate",
        "question": "Which is the correct translation of Zorro?",
        "options": [
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Dog"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Sword"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Fox"
          ],
          [
            "Zorro",
            "Coyote"
          ]
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select-item",
        "question": "Which 1971 film, known for its violence, was the first to use Dolby sound?",
        "options": [
          "Straw Dogs",
          "Dirty Harry",
          "A Clockwork Orange",
          "Play Misty for me"
        ],
        "answer": [2]
      },
      {
        "type": "picker",
        "question": "How many counters does a backgammon player have?",
        "min": 0,
        "max": 30,
        "answer": 15
      },
      {
        "type": "true-false",
        "question": "There is a patron saint of The Internet.",
        "answer": true
      },
      {
        "type": "alpha-picker",
        "question": " Which letter other than X scores 8 in Scrabble?",
        "answer": "J"
      },
      {
        "type": "four-quarter",
        "question": "Four of the worst ten maritime disasters all took place in 1945. In which sea were all four ships sunk?",
        "options": [
          "Mediterranean sea",
          "Baltic Sea",
          "The Bermuda Triangle",
          "Black Sea"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "What nut is used to flavor marzipan?",
        "options": [
          "Walnut",
          "Almond",
          "Cashew",
          "Pistachio"
        ],
        "answer": [1]
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  }
]
